◆深影字幕组原创译制
◆ 翻译
姜酱 二喵becky
◆翻译
Echo Zawiah
◆校对
小滔
◆后期
滔滔
◆监制
小滔
◆深影字幕组原创译制
◆ 翻译
姜酱 二喵becky
◆翻译
Echo Zawiah
◆校对
小滔
◆后期
滔滔
◆监制
小滔
美国梦工厂动画公司
功夫熊猫
漫漫阶梯
Stairs...
我觉得我快不行了
I don't think I can...
兄弟们 你们先行一步
Hey, guys, just start without me.
我稍后就来
I'll catch up.
舒坦
Sweet.
波澜不惊 方能心如止水
Inner peace. Inner peace.
鼻子好痒
Itchy nose.
阿嚏
Ah-choo!
终于 静心了
Finally, inner peace.
又怎么了
Now, what?
天煞 老朋友
Kai, old friend.
乌龟大师
Master Oogway.
你我之争早在五百年前就结束了
Our battle ended 500 years ago.
可我已经准备好再比一场了
Well, now I'm ready for a rematch.
你准备得可真够久的 哈哈哈
Took you long enough. Ha ha ha ha...
呀啊
Yaaa!
你的确变强了
You've grown stronger.
五百年灵界的修炼 不是白练的
500 years in the Spirit Realm, you pick up a thing or two.
我已经夺走了灵界每个大师的气
I have taken the Chi of every Master here.
- 不 - 是的
- No! - Yes.
很快你的力量也是我的了
And soon I will have your power too.
你何时才能领悟 索取越多 收获越少
When will you realize, the more you take, the less you have.
有了你的气 我终于又可以重回凡界
With your Chi, I will finally be able to return to the mortal world,
这一次 你阻止不了我了
And this time, you won't be there to stop me.
噢 阻止你从来都不是我的使命
Ah, it was never my destiny to stop you.
我已经有了一个好的人选
I have set another on that path.
那我就找到他 然后把他的气也夺走
Then I will find him, and take his Chi too.
正义就要得到伸张了
Justice, is about to be served.
给我们来两份正义套餐 谢谢
We'll have two justice platters , please
- 呃 三份 - 三份 - 再要几个豆腐花
- umm...three - Three. - And a few tofu buns.
还要一碗香辣拌面 给娇虎的 你要另外加酱料吗
Oh, the spicy noodle soup for Tigress. Did you want extra sauce with that?
她要分开放
She wants it on the side
- 分开 - 分开放
- On the side. - On the side.
神龙 你能做到
Dragon, you can do it.
- 冲吧 神龙大侠 - 保卫村庄
- Go, Dragon Warrior. - Defend the valley.
- 去呀 神龙大侠 - 保卫村庄
- Go Dragon Warrior. - Yeah, defend the valley
啊哒
Yee-ha!
你们没摆霸气的造型 对吧
You guys aren't doing the dramatic pose , are you?
我们需要每次出场都摆个造型吗
Do we have to strike a pose every time we land?
大伙儿 永远不要低估霸气登场的威力
You guys, never underestimate the power of a dramatic entrance.
我听说某些大师只靠破门之势
I've heard about some Masters who could win a fight
就能闪瞎对手赢得战斗
just by throwing open a door
嘿呀
Shuh-sha!
霸气登场
Dramatic entrance?
师傅
Master Shifu
神龙大侠说得对
The Dragon Warrior is correct.
是吗 我只是随口... 啊对 我就这个意思
Really? I was just making.... yeah, I mean, yeah, I am.
双方交战先比气势 后比拳头
Before the battle of the fist comes the battle of the mind.
因此 出场就是要霸气
Hence...the dramatic entrance.
哇 好霸气的登场
Whoa ,nice dramatic entrance.
- 今天是什么日子呀 - 今天将是我的最后一堂课
- What's the occasion? - Today will be my final class.
你的最后...等等 我都不知道你病了
Your final...? Wait. I didn't even know you were sick.
- 虽然你看上去是有点... - 我没病
- Although you have been looking a little.... - I'm not sick.
健康 有点健康 应该说很健康
healthy. A little healthy. A lot actually.
之所以是最后一课
My final class because from now on...
是因为接下来 负责你们训练的将会是神龙大侠
your training will be in the hands of the Dragon Warrior.
什么
What?
我来教 为什么不是娇虎
Me? teach? I mean why not Tigress?
她总是喜欢吆喝别人做这个做那个
She's always telling everyone what to do.
- 闭嘴 阿宝 - 看到了吧
- Be quiet Po. - See what I mean?
娇虎不是神龙大侠 你才是
Tigress is not the Dragon Warrior. You are.
别闹了 他们可是盖世五侠 我能教他们什么呀
Come on they're the Five. What can I teach them?
学海无涯 就连师傅也是
There is always something more to learn. Even for a Master.
打个比方 我来教你另一招
For instance, let me show you another move.
华丽退场
The dramatic exit.
那是啥
What's that?
哇
Whoa!
你在开玩笑吗 这...
Are you kidding me? That....what?
- 他去哪儿了 - 师傅
- Where'd he go? - Master.
他已经走啦 别那么严肃
- He's gone guys. It's cool.
听从您的指点 师傅
- We await your instruction, Master.
你若教不好 最多不被我们尊敬
All you have to lose is our respect.
说实话 能有多糟糕呢
Seriously, how bad could it be?
很糟糕 糟糕透了
Very bad! Very, very bad!
好了 我们换别的招式 金猴 使出稳如泰山
Okay. Okay, let's switch it up. Monkey, Immovable Mountain Stance.
是 师傅
Yes, Master.
- 我是说... 娇虎 旋风后空翻 - 是 师傅
- I mean.... Tigress, Tornado back flip. - Yes, Master.
- 噢不 火 - 开火
- Oh no, fire. - Fire.
抱歉 我的错 仙鹤再飞高点 啊不 低一点
Sorry, my fault. Crane go high, I mean low.
啊 我的小钳子
Oh, my claw thingy.
呃 灵蛇和娇虎 来一招虎啸蛇盘
Uh, Viper and tigress , to... like a totem pole.
放毒 进攻
Poison , Technique.
你们俩 使出白鹤亮翅 猴子摘桃 黄尾巴 黄马褂...
You two, to... Sworming insect bite with yellow tail , Yellow jacket...
香辣...金枪鱼
Spicy....tuna.
你干的好事 阿宝
Good job, Po.
啊
Ah.
你有学到一点点东西吗
Did you at least learn a little something?
有 你不是当老师的料
Yes , that you can't teach.
还有 原来娇虎是易燃物
And tigress is flammable, turns out.
简直惨不忍睹
That was a complete disaster.
- 我真庆幸自己不是阿宝 - 他真是一无是处
- I'm glad we're not Po right now. - What a loser.
不知道师傅是怎么想的
- What was Shifu thinking?
乌龟大师又是怎么想的
- What was Oogway thinking?
- 我觉得被他听到了 - 我啥都没听到
- I think he heard us. - I didn't hear anything.
他说你一无是处
He said you're a loser.
对不起 乌龟
Sorry, Oogway.
- 你能不能别这样了 - 你的第一课感觉如何
- Would you stop doing that? - How was your fisrt day teaching?
- 超丢脸 - 我听说了
- Humiliating. - I heard.
谁告诉你的 是娇虎吗
Who told you? Did Tigress tell you?
金猴 仙鹤 螳螂 你爸和隔壁礼品店的周大妈
I heard from Monkey and Crane and Mantis and your dad and Mrs. Chau from the gift shop
还有刚走过的那群鸭子以及娇虎告诉我的
And those ducks who just passed and Tigress told me.
好吧 那她有没有告诉你我以后再也不会了
Yeah, well did she also tell you that it'll never happen again cause I'm done?
你是指授课 还是丢脸
Teaching, or being humiliated?
都是 我都不知道你为什么认为我能教他们呢
Both. I don't know why you ever thought I could teach that class?
我就知道你不行
Oh, I knew you couldn't.
啥 你故意的吗 为什么
What? You set me up to fail? Why?
如果你只做你力所能及的事 你就没法进步
If you only do what you can do you'll never be more than you are now.
我不想要进步了 我这样就很好
I don't wanna be more. I like who I am.
你连自己是谁都不知道
You don't even know who you are.
你说啥 我当然知道 我是神龙大侠
What do you....? Of course I do. I'm the Dragon Warrior.
那神龙大侠究竟意味着什么呢
And what exactly does that mean Dragon Warrior?
意味着...我要四处闯荡 拳打脚踢
It means...you know... just going around and punching and kicking
保卫家园什么的
Defending the valley and stuff.
拳打脚踢
Punching and kicking?
你认为这就是乌龟大师看中你的原因吗
You think that is what the great Master Oogway saw for you?
一个五百年的预言选中了你
A five hundred year prophecy full-filled
难道就是让你耍耍花拳绣腿
so you can spend your days...
满镇子乱跑跟兔子耍帅吗
Kicking butt? And running through town high-fiving bunnies?
- 不是吗 - 不是
- Yes. - No!
阿宝 乌龟与我的意见相悖 他在你身上看到了潜能
Oogway saw greatness in you, Po, against my better judgement.
比你想象的还要多
More than you can see in yourself.
有一种神功等着你去发掘
Incredible power awaits you.
这种神功强大到你无法想像
Power beyond anything you can imagine.
哇噢
Whoa!
- 这是什么神功 - 这就是气功
- What was that? - That was chi.
哇噢 气是啥
Whoa! What's chi?
世间万物流转的能量就是气
The energy that flows through all living things.
所以你的意思是 如果我当了他们的老师
So you're saying if I, so you're saying if I teach,
我就可以练成这种神功了吗
I'll be able to do cool stuff like that?
不 我是说如果你当了他们的老师后
No, I'm saying if you teach,
我就可以练成这种神功了
I'll be able to do cool stuff like that.
- 噢 - 气的运用需要自我修炼
- Oh. - Mastery of chi requires Mastery of self.
乌龟曾在一个山洞里打坐整整三十年
Oogway sat alone in a cave for thirty years
只为弄清一个问题
asking one question....
我是谁
Who am I?
如果你能安静五分钟让我说完就好了
I'm lucky if I get 5 minutes before you interrupt.
所以我现在要找个山洞呆上三十年吗
So now I have to sit alone in a cave for thirty years?
总归要的 当你完成授课的时候
Eventually. After you Master teaching.
授课 我根本不可能做到像你这样
Teaching? There's no way I'm ever gonna be like you.
我没让你变成我这样
I'm not trying to turn you into me.
我是让你变成你自己
I'm trying to turn you into you.
让我变成我自己 等会儿 这没道理啊...
Turn me into me? Wait a second. That makes no....
加把劲 师傅 说得再玄乎一点 你就是下一个乌龟了
Almost there Shifu , just a little more confusing and you'll be the next Oogway.
噢 啊
Oh. Ah.
抱歉 乌龟大师 无意冒犯...
Sorry, no offense Master Oogway I just....
我就不打扰您的安宁了
I'll let you get back to your eternal peace.
- 这是哪儿 - 呃 我哥哥的菜地
- What is this place? - Aaah...my brother's farm?
哦 那如果我踩你一脚 你会死吗
Ah. If I stepped on you, would you die?
会
Yes.
这就是凡界
The mortal realm.
你听到了吗 乌龟 我回来了
You hear that Oogway? I'm back.
天煞回来了
Kai has returned.
- 谁 - 天煞 所向披靡的天煞
- Who? - Kai. General Kai.
这片神州大地最高的统帅
Supreme warlord of all China.
没听过
I don't know.
追魂翡翠 苦难之源
The jade slayer, Master of pain.
那你至少应该听过复仇之兽吧
You may know me as the beast of vengeance.
寡妇制造者呢
Maker of widows?
好吧 我以前跟乌龟是战友
Ok, I used to work with Oogway.
哦 乌龟大师 他可是名副其实的战士
Oh, Master Oogway, he was a great warrior.
我们知道乌龟大师 又智慧又...
- We've heard of Master Oogway. Wise and...
好了好了 够了
- Ok, ok, enough.
闭嘴
Silence!
找到乌龟的弟子 全部抓来见我
Find Oogway's students and bring them to me.
等我夺走了他们的气 乌龟...
By the time I am done with them, Oogway...
这世上就没人会记得你的名字了
There will be no one left to who will even remember your name.
哈哈哈 我天煞来了
Ha ha ha! Kai is coming!
我准备好了...
I am ready...
- 来教训你了 - 教训我
- to teach you a lesson. - Teach me?
- 哦不 是神龙大师 - 妈呀他太帅了
- Oh no, ite's the Dragon teacher. - Yeah he's so handsome.
多谢夸奖
Thank you for the compliment.
不 绕我一命吧
No, please don't teach me to death.
阿宝
Po?
嗨老爸 你好吗
Oh, hey dad. What's up?
我只是 回家泡个澡而已
I like just .... stopping by for a little soak.
- 说吧 出什么事啦 - 没事
- Okay , What's wrong? - Nothing.
没事 我回家发现你在这跟你的娃娃鸳鸯戏水...
Nothing? I come home to find you taking a bath with your dolls...
- 是人偶 - 而且加的不是浴盐
- Action figures. - And instead of adding bath-salt to the water.
- 反而加了四川辣椒面 - 啥 四川辣椒面
- You just added szechuan peppercorns. - Szechuan, what?
噢 噢 我白嫩的小屁股
Oh, oh, oh... my tenders.
好啦 我是有心事
Okay, yes, something's wrong.
乖儿子 告诉爸爸发生了什么事
There, there, son , you tell your daddy all about it.
胳膊抬起来
Lift your arm.
师傅说我还不知道神龙大侠的意义
Shifu says I don't know what it means to be the Dragon Warrior.
现在我居然还要当老师了
And now I have to be a teacher?
我以为我找到了自我
I thought I finally knew who I was.
可如果我不是神龙大侠 那么我又是谁呢
If I'm not the dragon Warrior, then who am I?
老师 教人功夫吗
A teacher? Teaching kung fu?
阿宝 这可是份美差啊 还犹豫啥 儿子
Po, that's a promotion. Take the job, son.
等有一天 你掌管了翡翠宫
And someday, when you're in charge of the whole Jade palace,
我就可以在大厅里卖面条了 哟呼
I can sell noodles in the lobby. Yoohoo.
你怎么还在这泡澡 跟个娃娃似的
Why are you still here taking a bath like a baby?
起来 起来 赶紧去干活
Get out. Get up. Go, go, go.
我们的店面就要扩张啦
- Franchise expansion awaits us!
那神龙大侠模仿大赛怎么办
- What about the Dragon Warrior look alike contest?
- 反正周大妈每次都赢 - 接招吧
- Mrs. Chau always wins that. - Skadoosh.
那神龙大侠吃包子大赛呢
And the Dragon Warrior dumpling eating contest?
我要保持我的不败记录
I have to defend my title.
没有人能打破你吃包子的记录
No one's gonna beat your dumpling eating record.
有人要打破你吃包子的记录啦
Someone's about to beat your dumpling eating record.
加油 加油
Go. Go. Go.
- 谁在吃我的包子 - 账算在谁头上
- Who's eating my dumplings? - And who's paying for them?
一百零一 一百零二
101, 102.
一百零三
103.
耶
Yeah!
新纪录吗
Is that a new record?
你是谁
Who are you?
- 我是李山 - 什么
- I'm Li Shan - What?
我叫李山
I'm Li shan.
我在找我儿子
I'm looking for my son.
- 你儿子不见了 - 是啊 多年以前丢的
- You lost your son? - Yes, many years ago.
- 我也跟我爸爸失散了 - 真抱歉
- I lost my father. - Very sorry.
谢谢你
Thank you.
好吧 祝你好运
Well , good luck to you.
你也是 希望你能找到你儿子
You too. I hope you find your son.
我也希望你能找到你爸爸
And I hope you find your father.
- 儿子 - 哈
- Son? - Huh?
我的天啊 真是你
Oh my gosh, it is you.
别傻站着呀 快给你老爸一个拥抱
Well, don't just stand there! Give your old man a hug!
不敢相信你还活着
I can't believe you're alive.
- 耶 - 耶
- Yeah! - Yeah!
我以为我永远地失去你了 小莲花
I thought I'd lost you forever, Little Lotus.
好吧 这下有点尴尬了
Oh, Okay. This is very embarrassing,
我想你认错儿子了 我不叫莲花 我叫阿宝
but I think you've got me confused with a panda named Lotus. My name is Po.
啊对了 你也许...
Oh right, you wouldn't... Okay.
这么说吧 小莲花是你的乳名
See, Little Lotus was the name you were given at birth.
- 真的吗 - 真的
- Really? -Really.
难以置信 这么多年了终于找到你了
I can't believe it. After all these years and you're really here?
这简直太神奇了
This is amazing.
老爸 这位是...
Oh, Dad. Come say hi to...
呃 我不知道应该怎么称呼你
Um. I don't know--I don't know what I'm supposed to call you.
他刚才说他叫李山
I'm pretty sure he said his name is Li.
你 来抱抱
You...come here
太谢谢你了 把我的儿子照顾得那么好
Thank you, thank you for taking such good care of my son.
你的儿子 先等等
Your son? Now hold on just a minute.
我们怎么知道这个人跟你有没有联系
How do we know this stranger is even related to you?
你看啊 一看肚子就知道是自家人
Look at that. Our bellies could be brothers.
嘿儿子 我来教你怎么拱肚子 来 拱肚子
Hey son, let me teach you how to Belly Gong. All right, belly gong.
太酷炫了 它们震动的频率还一致
That's so cool. They jiggle the same.
好像在照镜子一样
It's like looking in a fat mirror.
真想不到 我们还能一起合影
I can't believe we're taking a picture together.
我还是不明白 我以为阿宝是最后一只熊猫了
But I still don't understand. I thought Po was the only panda left.
- 不 还有一大群呢 - 在哪
- No, there's a whole bunch of us. - Where?
- 就在山里的神秘熊猫村里 - 神秘熊猫...
- Here, a secret panda village in the mountains. - A secret panda....
哇噢
Whoa.
可是你是怎么知道我在这的
But how did you know where I was?
我收到的消息指引我来的
I received a message that led me here.
如果没人找得到你 你是怎么收到消息的
How could you receive a message if no one could find you?
太可疑了
Sounds suspicious to me.
不 等等 这是一则来自宇宙的消息
No, wait, wait. It was a message from the universe.
- 哦哦哦哦 - 哇噢
- Ooooooh! - Whoa!
- 哇噢 - 扯淡
- Whoa. - Rats.
现在说说 神龙大侠是怎么一回事啊
Now, what's all this about a Dragon Warrior?
你怎么知道我就是神龙大侠 是宇宙告诉你的吗
How'd you know I was the Dragon Warrior? Did the universe tell you that, too?
海报上写着呢 还有礼品店 我买了一个小杯杯
No, the poster did, and the gift shop. I bought a tiny cup.
哦 对 当然了
Oh right, of course...
你得看看...你不知道我有多少东西要给你看
You gotta... you have no idea there's so much to show you.
你会为我自豪的
You're gonna be so awesomely proud!
来呀 来呀
Come on! Come on!
我已经很为你自豪了
I'm already awesomely proud.
- 还有几级就到了 - 噢
- Oh. Couple more steps. - Oh.
我感觉脂肪在燃烧
Feeling the burn.
你也有熊猫哮喘综合征吗 我们是不是家族遗传啊
Do you have panda asthma, too? Does that run in the family?
爸 你肯定会爱上这儿的
Dad, you're gonna love this.
这里有最炫酷的东西
It's like the coolest thing ever.
这就是英雄之殿
This is the hall of heroes.
收藏了武林中所有的奇珍异宝
Home of the most priceless kung fu artifacts in all of China.
哇噢 这儿真是...
Whoa. This place is ....
太棒了 你准备这样说对吧
Awesome? You were going--you were going to say awesome, right?
- 因为真是太棒啦 - 太棒啦
- Because it totally is! - Totally!
不过你要超级小心 这里都是些易碎品
But be super careful, everything is very fragile here.
比如说这个装着武士耳语的灵坛
Like the Urn of Whispering warriors.
就有人打碎过
Someone broke that once.
- 谁 - 某个傻子
- Who? - Some idiot.
哇噢
Wow!
这是飞天犀牛大师的战甲
- This is Master flying Rhino's battle armor.
我很好奇我能不能塞进去
- I wonder if I could fit in that.
你是我肚子里的蛔虫吗 老爸 我跟你想的一样
Get out of my head, dad. I've wondered the same thing.
想知道我穿不穿得下
- If I could fit in it?
你穿不穿得下 不 是我穿不穿得下
-If you could? No, if I could fit in it.
老爸 过来看看这个
Dad, check it out.
公羊大师的十字弩 破过无数道城门
Master Ram's crossbow. The infinite gates smasher.
老爸 再来看看这个
Dad, look at this.
老鼠大师军团的兜鍪 真的很小
The battle helmets of Master Rat's army. They're so tiny.
海豚大师的防水盔甲 这是我的最爱
Master Dolphin's water proof armor. This is my favorite.
看 这是传说中的雄鹰大帝的战车
Check it out. It's the legendary battle rickshaw of emperor Hawk
车很拉风
Sweet ride.
爸 你在做什么 任何东西都是禁止触摸的
Dad, what are you doing? We're not supposed to touch anything.
抱歉 我应该要放回原处吗
Sorry, sorry. Should I put it back?
对 你应该要放回去 不过你这样帅呆了
Yeah, you probably should. You look so cool, though.
感觉如何 紧身不 里面有犀牛的味道吗
How does it feel? Do the hinges hinge? Does it smell like rhino?
有觉得自己坚不可摧吗
Does it feel like you're impenetrable?
有觉得自己能够以一敌千
Does it feel like you can take on a thousand warriors
却毫发无损吗
and emerge unscathed?
对 感觉很酷
Yes, it's pretty cool.
这有什么用 拉拉试试
What this does? I should pull it.
我激动尿了
I think I just peed a little.
还有什么好玩的可以试试吗 儿子
Anything else we should try in here, son?
进攻
Charge!
快点 快点 再快点
Faster, faster, faster!
- 拇指大战 - 援军来了
- Thumb war! - Reinforcements!
太好玩了
This is so much fun...
- 开始转了 - 太棒了
- Here we go. - Awesome!
- 吐吧吐吧 - 我没事 没事
- There, there - I'm fine, I'm fine.
吐出来就没事了
There you go.
海豚穿心剑
Dolphin style attack!
- 命中 - 海豚大挪移
- You got me. - Dolphin style retreat!
准备好了 儿子
Go long son.
我还没准备好呢
I wasn't ready.
- 接好了 - 接住了
- Coming back at you. - I got it.
- 往上抛 - 来了 接好了
- Throw it high! - Here you go. Yeah, C'mon.
- 我要来了 - 那就来吧 犀牛大师
- I'm coming for you. - Bring it on Master Rhino.
我来了
Here I come!
我要追上你了 追上你
I'm gonna get you. I'm gonna get you.
追上你
I'm gonna get you.
停停停
Shh, stop.
谁会追上你 谁追上你了
Who's gonna get you? Who's gonna get you?
- 犀牛大师 - 怎么 怎么了
- Master Rhino. - Why, what's wrong?
你们好
Hello.
大伙 你们永远也猜不到他是谁
Guys guys, you're never gonna guess who just showed up.
不会一辈子也猜不到
Not in a million years.
只是你们不可能... 你们猜猜
You can't.... you just try.
- 你爸爸 - 你爸爸
- Your father! - Your father!
怎么都一猜就中
Wow, how did you just guess that?
好吧 当然会猜到 我们看起来简直一模一样
Oh, wait a second. Yeah of course. We look exactly the same.
老爸 跟我朋友打声招呼吧
Dad. Say hi to my friends,
这是螳螂 娇虎 金猴 仙鹤 还有灵蛇
Mantis, Tigress, Monkey, Crane, and Viper.
- 你是灵蛇 对吗 - 我是金猴 大叔
- Oh, Viper, was it? - Monkey, sir.
他们是我最好的朋友
They're kind of my best friends.
这...这位是师傅 他是个传奇
And this... this is Master Shifu. Legend.
很荣幸见到你 熊猫大师
It is an honor to meet you, Master Panda.
或许你爸爸愿意随我们一起到练功房
Perhaps your father would care to join us in the training hall?
您儿子要给他们上课
Your son will be teaching the class.
他肯定很累 你一定很累
I'm sure he's tired. I'm sure you're tired.
他累了 我带他去菊花房休息
He's tired. I'm gonna show him the chrysanthemums suite.
什么 累 不 一定也不累 我很想看你教课
What? Tired? No, I'm fine. I would love to watch you teach.
相信我 看我教课一点也不有趣...
Trust me. It would be more fun to watch me...
- 战斗 - 那是什么
- Fight! - What is that?
村子被人攻击了
The valley is under attack.
- 儿子 被攻击 - 这太棒了
- Son? Under attack? -This is perfect!
这下你就要见识神龙大侠的厉害了
Now you can see what being the dragon warrior is all about.
跟我来
Follow me!
你们这群恶徒 准备...
Enemies of justice. Prepare for....
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
痛
Ow!
这些绿家伙是什么玩意儿
What's the deal with the green guys?
- 某种翡翠僵尸 - 翡翠僵尸
- Some kind of jade zombies. - Jade zombies?
- 翡尸 就是这个 - 翡尸 就是这个
- Jombies, Jinx. - Jombies, Jinx.
小莲花 小心点
- Lotus, be careful!
爸 没事 这事我每天都在做...
- It's Okay, Dad. I do this everyday...!
我认识他们 他们是双獾大师
I recognize this guys. The Master Badger twins.
和他们的双击绝招
With their crushing double gong technique.
对 就是这个 那个是...不是吧
Yeah, that's the one. That guys is.... no
豪猪大师
Master Porcupine.
他不是几百年前就去世了吗
I thought he died hundred years ago?
全是传奇人物
These guys are legends.
来张速写
Get a quick sketch of us.
画好了吗 画好了吗
Did you get it? Did you get it?
我眨眼了 能再画一张吗
I blinked. Can we get another one?
我要被豪猪大师掐死了 简直太帅了
I'm being choked by Master Porcupine. This is so cool.
- 看 是你 - 阿宝 专心点
- Look. It's you. - Po, focus!
宇宙消息 那我再来给你条宇宙消息吧
Message from the universe. I'll give you one message from the universe...
离我儿子远点
Stay away from my son.
抱歉 爸 稍后我会清干净
Sorry dad. I'll clean it up later.
小心点 别用我的好锅 用这个
Whoa, whoa, not my good pan. Take this one.
小莲花小心
Lotus, watch out!
老爸 看我的无敌连环包
Dad, check out my dumplings of doom.
抓到了
Gotcha!
我看见你们了
I see you.
你们的气很快就是我的了
Your chi will soon be mine.
- 他在跟我说话吗 - 哪个 他们三个都在说话
- Is he talking to me? - Which one? They're all talking.
对 太恐怖了
You're right. That's so scary.
我们应该也要试试看 说不定能反过来吓唬他们
We should try that, too. Maybe it'd be scary back at them.
好 不过我们得先商量好应该怎么说
Okay, but we gotta plan what we're gonna say first,
要不然的话 那就不是可怕了 而是蠢了
otherwise it won't be scary, it'll be just stupid.
不是他们在说话 白痴
It's not them talking, you idiots!
是我在通过他们说话 我是天煞
It's me talking through them, Kai!
- 谁 - 好好 够了
- Who? - Okay, okay, enough.
- 看到了吗 看到了吗 - 发生了什么
- Did you see that? Did you see? - What just happened?
那些绿烟就咻的一下 又咻地消失了
The green smoke just poof.... and then poof.
师傅 那是什么
Shifu, what wast that?
天煞 天煞 天煞 是谁呢
Kai? Kai? Kai?
不知道 没听过
Nope. Never heard of him.
天煞 天煞 在哪里
Kai... Kai... Where is it?
这里太多装满智慧的卷轴了 什么都找不到
There's so much wisdom in here, I can't find anything.
找到了
Yes!
看好了
Behold.
所有答案都将在这里找到
All the answers will be found within.
什么 一片空白
What? It's blank?
是在耍我吗 又来这套
Are you kidding me? Not again.
等等 等一下 抱歉 好了 我们开始吧
Wait, wait. Hold on. Sorry, okay, here we go.
是乌龟亲手写的
It is written in Oogway's hand.
- 很久以前 我有一个兄弟 - 乌龟竟然有兄弟
- Long ago, I had a brother. - Oogway had a brother?
战友 是战友 抱歉
In arms. In arms, sorry.
他写的是兄弟般的战友
- He says brother in arms.
你就不能一次性展开卷轴吗
- Can't you just unroll it all at once?
我曾是一名雄心勃勃的年轻战士 带领一支伟大的军队
I was an ambitious young warrior leading a great army.
与我并肩作战的就是天煞
And fighting by my side was Kai.
我最亲密的朋友
My closest friend.
有一天 我们遭到了埋伏 我身负重伤
One day we were ambushed. I was badly wounded.
我的朋友背着我日以继夜地寻求帮助
My friend carried me for days looking for help.
最后我们来到一个高山上的神秘村庄
Until we came to a secret village, high in the mountains.
古老的疗伤圣地
An ancient place of healing.
全村都是熊猫
A village of pandas.
- 熊猫 - 对 熊猫
- Pandas? - Yes, pandas.
熊猫他们用气功治好了我
Pandas who used the power of chi to heal me.
他们还教会我如何释放气
They taught me how to give chi.
但天煞想独占所有气
But Kai, wanted the power all to himself.
他发现气既能被给予 也能被夺走
He saw that what could be given could also be taken.
我必须阻止他
I had to stop him.
我们打得山摇地动
Our battle shook the Earth.
最终 我将他打入灵界
Until, finally, I banished Kai to the Spirit Realm.
若他重返人间
Should he ever return to the mortal realm,
唯有真正的气功大师才能阻止他
he can only be stopped by a true Master of chi.
真正的气功大师 比如你
True Master of chi? Like you.
我 我只能发功让花盛开而已
Me? I can barely make a flower bloom!
我至少还要在山洞里修炼三十年
I'd need at least thirty more years, and a cave.
我们需要一个气功大师
We need a chi Master.
他会继续夺走别的大师的气 世上就再也没气了
He will continue stealing the chi of Masters until he has consumed it all.
我们必须想办法阻止他
We have to make a way to stop him.
败下的大师越多 他得到的气也就越多
He gets more more powerful with every Master he defeats.
我们没别的选择 只能去战斗
There is no choice. We fight.
我可以教你 儿子
I can teach you, son.
- 你可以教我 - 当然 我是只熊猫
- You can do this? - Of course, I'm a panda.
这肯定是宇宙让你来的原因
That must be why the universe sent you here.
好 那我要做什么
Okay, so what do I have to do?
- 你要跟我回家 - 什么
- You have to come home with me. - What?
- 回到神秘村庄 - 对 儿子
- To the secret village? - Yes, son.
你必须重新学会如何做一只熊猫
You must rediscover what it is to be a panda.
你要学会如何像熊猫那样生活 像熊猫那样睡觉
You have to learn how to live like a panda. Sleep like a panda.
像熊猫那样吃东西
Eat like a panda.
103个包子 还没够我塞牙缝呢
Those 103 dumplings? I was just warming up.
我一直认为 我吃东西的潜力还没全部挖掘出来
I've always felt like I wasn't eating up to my full potential.
你不能把我们家阿宝带走 不不 我要别的意见
You can't take Po away from me. No, no I want a second opinion.
师傅 再开一卷吧
Shifu, open another scroll or something.
- 我觉得他应该去 - 好 再来个意见
- I think he should go. - Fine. A third opinion.
金猴 灵蛇 娇虎
Monkey? Viper? Tigress?
老爸 你也听到师傅说的和乌龟写的
Dad, you heard what Shifu said, Oogway said.
只有真正的气功大师才能阻止天煞
This guy can only be stopped by a Master of chi.
而我只有知道我究竟是谁才能学会用气
And I can only master chi by knowing who I really am.
我 我是熊猫
Well, I'm a panda.
我去给你准备路上的午餐
I'll pack your lunch for the road.
你真的认为阿宝能及时学会气功吗
Do you really think Po can master chi in time?
我的想法并不重要
Doesn't matter what I think.
- 宇宙怎么想才是最重要的 - 所以答案是不会
- It only matters what the universe thinks. - So, that's a "No"?
- 师傅 我们要做什么 - 你去查明天煞的下落
- Master, what are we going to do? - You are going to find out where Kai is.
寻着那些翡翠僵尸的踪迹 但千万别跟他打起来
Follow the trail of those jade creatures but do not engage.
因为天煞会越战越强
For with every foe he faces Kai becomes stronger.
为什么选我 是因为我多嘴吗
- Why me? Is it because I asked.
不是 因为你能飞
- No, it is because you can fly.
- 去吧 - 早知道就闭上你的鸟嘴了
- Go! - Should have kept your beak shut.
- 带上螳螂 - 什么 因为我插嘴...
- And take Mantis. - What? Oh man, is it because I ...?
对
Yes.
吃点东西吗
Oh, lunch break?
你不用同样问题问两遍
You don't need to ask me twice.
- 老爸 - 干嘛
- Dad? - Yes?
- 老爸 - 啥
你在这里干什么
- What are you doing here?
你说我在干什么 我背疼死了
- What am I doing? Getting a backache.
你非得在每块石头上踩着走吗
Did you have to step on every rock?
- 不 我是说你怎么在这 - 那你说我该怎么办
- No, I mean why are you here? - What was I supposed to do?
如果你不喜欢吃那些熊猫的东西怎么办
What if the pandas don't have food you like?
你饿着肚子的话 怎么去拯救世界呀
You're never gonna be able to save the world on an empty stomach.
我觉得我跟着你攸关成败
I consider my presence mission critical.
关于这点 我们不能告诉外人村庄的位置
Oh yes about that. We can't share the location of the village with others.
- 所以... - 你认为我守不住秘密 是吧
- So... - Well, you think I can't keep a secret, huh?
我养了阿宝二十年才告诉他 他不是我亲生的
I raised Po for 20 years before I finally told him he was adopted.
- 真的吗 - 真的
- Seriously? - Yeah.
好吧 我想 让你飞回去是有点残忍
Okay, I guess it would be cruel to make you fly back.
- 你竟然会飞 - 鹅也是鸟好吗 阿宝
- You can fly? - I'm a bird, Po.
我们到了
We're here.
看上去还要很长一段路
Sure looks like a long ways up there.
我儿子最讨厌爬阶梯了 我们还是回家吧
And my son hates stairs. So, let's go home.
我们可是熊猫 我们才不爬阶梯
We're pandas. We don't do stairs.
我一辈子都在等着这句话
I've waited my whole life to hear those words.
扯淡
Rats.
这就是神秘熊猫村 难怪你们要保密
This is the secret panda village? No wonder you keep it a secret.
如果我住在这 我也不好意思告诉别人
If I lived here, I wouldn't tell anyone either.
现在你可以"哇"了
Now you can whoa.
李山 大家注意 李山回来了
Li? Everyone, Li is back.
- 回来了两个人 - 他找到儿子了
- They're both back. - He found his son.
- 他做到了 - 他们回来了
- He made it. - They're back.
- 李山 - 他找到他儿子了
- Li? - He found his son.
大家 李山回来了
Everyone, Li is back.
等等 我们来了
Hang on, we're coming.
他做到了
He made it.
- 他成功了 - 为什么我们要跑
- He made it! - Why are we running?
- 他做到了 - 李山回来了
- He made it. - Li shan is back.
大家都围过来吧 这是我儿子
Everyone, everyone gather around. This is my son.
- 你们好 - 真可爱
- Hello. Hi. - Cute.
- 三胞胎 - 嗨 我是酷酷
- Triplets! - Hi, I'm Ku Ku.
- 我是萌萌 - 我是帅帅 他闻起来像饼干
- I'm Meng Meng. - I'm Shuai Shuai, he smells like cookies.
- 他好帅啊 跟他老爸一样帅 - 谢谢夸奖
- He's so handsome. Just like his father. - Thank you.
儿子 他们是你的表哥 点点和心心
Son, these are your cousins. Dim and Sum.
- 我竟然有表哥 - 欢迎 - 欢迎
- I have cousins. - Welcome. - Welcome.
- 串在一起的包子 - 我们叫它小吃项链
- Buns on a string. - We call it a snacklace.
没错
That's right.
我们会再给你做一条
We'll make you another one.
是你啊
It's you.
- 很高兴见到你 嗨 - 其实我不认识你
- So, that's nice to see you. Hi. - I don't know who you are.
花娃娃 好漂亮啊
Stripey baby So beautiful.
小心点 那是我的人偶
Okay, careful with that. That's my action figure.
能送我吗
Can I keep her?
- 不 - 行吗
- Noooo... - Can I?
没...问题 当然没问题 我带来就是要送给你的
No....problem. Of course, yeah that's why I brought her.
- 好好照顾她 - 肯定会 花娃娃
- Take good care of her. - Yes, stripey baby
你看起来就像婴儿版的我
You look just like me but a baby.
你就像老年版的我 你就是胖点的我
You're like me but old. You're like me but fatter.
你像
You're like me but...
戴着帽子的我
with a hat.
他确实戴着帽子
He does wear a hat.
你们看起来都和我一样
You all look like me.
我们去大吃一顿吧 庆祝我儿子回来了
Let's feast in my son's honor.
- 这是什么 - 熊猫不用走的 我们滚吧
- What the.....? - Pandas don't walk! We roll!
你有见过这么可笑的人吗
How you ever seen anyone look so ridiculous?
阿宝 你在干什么 阿宝
Po, what are you doing? Po?
你说得对 的确比走路强多了
You're right. That is better than walking.
- 对 - 好东西
- Yeah. - That's nice stuff.
吃点包子吧
Yeah, have some dumplings.
哪有不会滚的熊猫呀
What kind of panda doesn't know how to roll?
在当熊猫这方面 我还是新人
Well, I'm kinda new at this whole being a panda thing.
你是什么品种的熊猫啊 你脖子好搞笑
Hey, what kind of panda are you? You have a funny neck.
我根本不是熊猫
I'm not a panda at all.
- 那是什么  - 我的帽子
- What's that? - My hat
- 那个呢   - 我的嘴
What's that? - My beak
- 那个呢 - 我的翅膀
What's that? , - My wing
- 那个呢  - 我的包子
- What's that? - My dumplings.
别再问问题了 坐好 小屁孩
No more questions. Go away, kid.
- 儿子 给你 我给你带了筷子 - 谢谢你 老爸
- Here, son, I packed your chopsticks. - Thanks, dad.
- 怎么了 - 那是干什么用的
- What? - What are those for?
这个 这是筷子 用来夹包子
These? These are chopsticks. They're for picking up dumplings.
你是说 你只一口一个包子
You mean you only eat one at a time?
我就知道我在吃方面潜力无限
I knew I wasn't eating up to my potential.
我是美美
I am Mei Mei.
她真是花容月貌 美若天仙
She's amazing. She's so beautiful.
嘴真甜 阿宝 不过留着些好话
That's sweet, Po, but please try to save all
等我表演完了再夸
other compliments until after the performance.
我 不 我没说...
Me? No, I didn't say....
别说话 表演完再夸
Shut it. After the performance.
还没开始吗
Has it started yet?
全天下最棒的彩带舞者
Best ribbon dancer in the world.
- 至少她是这么说的 - 看那 看那
- At least that's what she says. - Look away, look away.
不行 你做不到 对吧
No, you can't. Can you?
老爸 为啥她一直那样盯着我看啊
Dad, why does she keep staring at me like that?
试着跟上姐的舞步
Try to keep up.
- 我真不知道怎么跳舞 - 你当然知道
- I don't really know how to dance. - Of course you do.
所有熊猫都会跳舞
All pandas dance.
- 我知道你在想什么 - 真的吗
- I know what you're thinking. - You do?
一只熊猫怎么能如此貌美呢
How can one panda be so beautiful?
- 哇哦 - 送我的 谢谢
- Whoa! - For me? Fine.
- 帮帮我 老爸 - 哦 不 你得自己来
- Help me, dads. -Yeah, no. You're on your own.
跳的不错 儿子
You're doing great, son.
该你了
Your turn.
把他带回家吧
Bring it home!
没关系 你会掌握窍门的
Don't worry, you'll get the hang of it.
我要学的东西多着呢
I have so much to learn.
追踪之翼
Wings of surveillance.
- 你说那个干嘛 - 说什么
- Why do you do that? - Do what?
就算你说"之翼"什么的
Just because you say "Wings of......"
也不代表你的动作有多特别
before something it doesn't mean that you're doing a special move.
就好像我说"强力之刃"或者
It's like me saying, "Antenna of power" or....
"三明治之喉"那样
" Thorax of making sandwiches"
- 反对之翼 - 哇 那里
- Wings of disagreement. - Whoa, there.
熊大师 鸡大师 鳄鱼大师 你们在这干嘛呢
Master Bear, Master Chicken, Master Croc, what are you doing out here?
翡翠军团袭击了我们的村庄 我们追到了这里
Jade creatures attacked our villages. We've tracked them here.
停下
Stop.
他们一定在里面
They must be in there.
师父让我们坚决
Master Shifu strongly advised us.....
- 不要和他交手 - 我们必须进去
- ...not to engage. - We got to get in there.
- 但师父说 - 你害怕了吗
- But Master Shifu said... - You're seriously afraid?
连鸡大师都进去了 他可是只鸡啊
Even Master Chicken's going in there and he's a chicken.
就这么定了 我要进去了
- That's it, I'm going in.
螳螂 我们有命令在身 不能
- Mantis, we have orders not to....
他们需要帮忙 快点 我从上方攻击 你从下面
They need our help. Come on. I'll go high, you go low.
别 等等
No, wait.
难道还怕只虫子
Fear the bug.
看着 你个小...
Alright, you little...!
- 坚持住 伙计 我来了 - "强力之刃"
- Hold on, buddy. I'm coming. - "Antenna of power"
- 啊 怎么不管用 - 螳螂
- Ah, it didn't work! - Mantis!
螳螂
Mantis?
你的气很强 和你的朋友一样 那个小虫子
Your chi is strong, just like your friend, the bug.
啊 螳螂
Huh? Mantis.
别担心 小鸟儿 我会让你的真气派上好用场的
Don't worry, little birdie. I'll put your chi to good use.
我将毁掉翡翠宫和它里面的每一个人
Destroying the Jade palace and everyone in it.
不可能
No.
悔过...之翼
Wings of...regret.
哦 没错 熊猫训练的第一天
Oh yeah, first day of panda training.
好了 花儿 我会让你开放的
Alright flower, I'm gonna make you bloom.
老爸 老爸
Dad, dad .
干嘛 干嘛 什么事啊
- What? What? What is it?
我准备好迎接第一天的熊猫训练啦
-I'm ready for my first day of panda training.
什么
What?
就是学着怎么做只熊猫啊 一位气功大师 拯救世界
You know, learn to be a panda, Master chi, save the world.
熊猫要睡到午后才起床的
Pandas sleep till past noon.
所以第一课就是回被窝接着睡
So lesson number one is go back to bed.
好吧
Of course.
没听说过这玩意这么简单
Nobody said this was gonna be easy.
- 我睡过头了吗 - 哈哈 当然
- Did I oversleep? - Ha, ha! You sure did.
好样的
Yes!
对了 孩子们 给他示范一下
Yeah, show him kids.
你能这样吗 能这样吗
Can you do this? Can you do that?
- 这样呢 还有这样呢 - 嘿
- How about this? How about that? - Hey?
- 我做的对吗 这样好不好呢
- Am I doing it? Is this good?
就这样 我会了
Here we go. I got it!
- 熊猫奶奶 小心头顶 - 噢
- Grandma panda, heads up. - Ow.
- 噢 - 我们还是打滚吧
- Oh. - We better roll.
阿宝 午饭时间到了
Po, lunchtime.
阿宝 你要顺其自然的滚才行啊
Po. You gotta let the hill tell you where to roll.
菜鸟都这样
- Rookie mistake.
点点 心心 让他看看我们是如何上山的吧
- Dim, Sum, let's show him how we go uphill.
- 太帅了 - 吃点心啦 噢
- It's beautiful. - Snack time. Oh.
- 阿宝 你会飞了 - 全速前进
- Po, you can fly? - I'm coming in hot!
那就等凉了再吃吧
Get them while they're cold.
你们在这干嘛 那些是给阿宝的
What are you doing there? That food is for Po.
下锅咯
Throw it in.
抱抱 抱抱 就这样
There, there, that's it.
- 感到放松了吗 - 嗯 是的
- Feeling relaxed? - Yeah, really.
- 只要顺其自然就好 - 懂了
- Just let yourself fall into it. - Got it.
我没事 我只是
I'm fine. I just.....
这就对了 都吐出来就好了
There we go. Just let it all out.
这才是我的好孩子
That's my boy.
出去
Get out of there!
我的面条 别动我的面条
My noodles. Leave my noodles alone.
- 讨厌 阿宝 真讨厌 - 我也要抱抱
- Subtle, Po. Very subtle. - Let me get some of that.
别吃我的帽子
And leave my hat alone.
- 我们爱吃面条 - 噢 多像阿宝小的时候啊
- We love noodles! - Oh, just like my Po.
你们看什么呢
What are you guys looking at?
我们就是这样滚的 发炮
That's how we roll. Cannonball.
哈哈 来了
Hoo-hoo. Yeah!
- 妈妈 看呀
- Mom, look it.
这次怎么样
How was that?
- 现在你再试一次 但别太用力 - 好的
- Now you try again but don't try so hard. - Okay, Okay.
好多了
Much better.
- 谢谢你 老爸 - 谢什么
- Thanks, dad. - For what?
你懂的 就是 告诉我做一只熊猫
You know, just for you know, showing me what it feels like...
是怎样的感觉
to be a panda.
那么你究竟认为我什么时候能准备充分呢
- So when do you think I'll be ready?
准备充分
- Ready?
就是学习怎样掌握气功呀
You know, to learn how to master chi.
很快 很快就可以了
Soon, real soon.
来吧 我想给你看点别的 跟我来
Come on. I wanna show you something else. C'mon
真不好意思 这里乱七八糟的 我这很少有来访者
Sorry about the mess, I don't usually get visitors.
这是我妈妈么
Is this my mom?
我在你百日的时候完成了这幅画像
I had this done on your one hundredth day.
你妈妈根本没法让你安静下来
Your mama couldn't hold you still.
你差点把这张纸给吃了
You nearly eat the paper.
- 真的 - 她什么样
- It's true. - What was she like?
她简直完美
She was the total package.
聪明 美丽
Smart, beautiful.
食量巨大
Tremendous appetite.
她是我一生的挚爱
She was the love of my life.
然后 就在我觉得人生达到最美满的时候
And then, just when I thought I couldn't get any luckier.
你降临了 我的小莲花
Along you came, my Little Lotus.
那时我真的拥有了世界的全部
I really had it all.
b>These are all Manuel Diaz's accounts?
娌￠. 姣澶╃伴瀛娆撅姣绗9000缇.
Yeah. Cash deposits made daily in $9,000 increments.
- 浠ラ惰归涓浼ュ. - .
- So, it doesn't have to be reported. - That's right.
浣芥ュ鸿浜璐疯ユ?
And you can seize that?
宸茬ㄥ浜. 浠瑕杩借釜杩浜垫风.
I already have. And I'll go through these wire transfer numbers and
骞跺荤浠璐.
freeze all these accounts as well.
缁浣.
Here you go.
- 浠濡锛澶＄句. - 涔浜?
- Damn, that's smart. - What?
杩惰淇￠搴锛
This is a bank line of credit.
浠ョㄦユ浠娆娆.
See, you make payments over what you owe,
瀹涓琛ㄧ颁负伴娴锛琛ㄧ颁负璐璐锋句棰.
and it doesn't show up as cash, it shows up as a negative loan balance.
ㄨ绉瑰浠浠姘歌戒浼琚惰ュ. 涓绠℃IRS杩DEA锛杩绗遍芥涓瑙.
It's never reported to anyone. IRS, DEA... This money is invisible.
浠澶灏?
How much does he have?
.
Take a look.
锛澶.
Oh, my God.
浠浠版1700涓缇.
They just seized $17 million.
- 杩涓濂, . - 浠涔?
- It's a bogus bust, Kate. - What?
浣璧疯涓浜浠. 杩浜瀛娆捐处蜂灞浜浠讳浜.
You can't prosecute it. No one controls who deposits money in an account.
涓涔寰甯灏变灏ｄ辨跺.
An attorney will have that money back in a few months,
宸茬寰澶浜哄杩杩浜浜.
but a lot of heads will roll before that.
浣浠板ㄤ跺浠ラ杩浜癸浠宠捣...
But we can arrest Manuel for now. We can get him off the street.
- 浠灏辨瑕璁╄开浜瑰板ㄨタワ杩.
We gotta get Manuel called back to Mexico. That's the objective...
浠ㄥㄨタユ病告绠¤.
We have no jurisdiction in Mexico.
- 浠浠涔芥病锛浠板ㄥ椤诲逛涔.
We have nothing. We need to do something now.
讳浠涓介浠.
Can't arrest him.
浠涔?
What?
浠涔跺?
When?
绛浼.
Wait a minute.
姣澶╅芥9000缇瀛杩杩涓璐.
$9,000 is deposited into this account every day in cash,
杩缁5骞.
for five years.
杩涓杩娉. 杩杩娉瀚锛浣涓杩娉.
That's not illegal. It's suspect, but it isn't illegal.
瑙寰IRS浼璁や负杩杩娉.
I think the IRS might think it's illegal.
浣宠浠涔, ?
What do you want, Kate? What would you like done here?
抽电фｇ‘绋搴ュ.
I want to follow some semblance of procedure.
ｅ氨宠.涓璧峰姝ｅ寮告瀹″.
That's what I want. To build a prosecutable case.
杩涓ゅ勾, 浠宸茬瀵硅涓板虹
We prosecuted more felony drug cases in this region last year
寰澶瀹涓ラ姣妗浠堕借琛浜姝ｅ寮告瀹″.
than in the two previous years combined.
浣浣板ㄨ蛋ㄨ涓锛炬?
Are you feeling that on the street?
板涓涓规浠疯浜姘?
You getting the vibe that we're winning?
娌℃.
No.
ｄ?
Do you?
涔娌℃锛垮.
No sir, I don't.
ㄩ┈硅风椤鹃.
Advisors like Matt come in, they stir the pot,
璁╀浠璧蜂绔, 杩浣块ｄ缃浣哄搴.
they cause the criminals to react and make mistakes.
浠插虹寸唤. 杩灏辨ㄨ烘浜涓.
That's how we build cases against the individuals
涓轰涔浠浼浠ュ涓妗规.
that actually make a difference in this fight.
褰浠浠绱у, 褰浠浠涓淇′换浠浠.
It's when they're nervous, when they stop trusting their crews,
褰浠浠杞绉讳浠璧娆.
when they move their money.
杩浜锛戒缁浠烘讳浠濂芥轰.
These are all opportunities to strike.
杩灏辨鹃┈硅浜浜哄浜.
And that's the purpose of people like Matt.
, 杩浜浜骞堕鸿涓浜烘.
Kate, this isn't something that I dreamed up myself.
骞舵病╂椤鹃锛
I don't have the authority to hire advisors,
浜哄ヤ妗灏缁锛
or authorize joint agency missions,
璁╂㈠ㄧ┖哄颁椋.
or fly agents from Air Force bases.
浣芥澶澧?
Are you understanding me?
杩涓芥遍ｄ
These decisions are made far from here
杩绂昏版圭褰灞冲. 浠.
by officials elected to office, not appointed to them.
姝ゅ浣蹇杩瓒烘寰浠ュ琛锛
So, if your fear is operating out of bounds,
板ㄥ璇浣,涓ㄦ蹇.
I am telling you, you are not.
ㄩ甯稿板甫锛ㄩ甯告娈.
The boundary's been moved.
娓妤浜?
Are we clear?
锛垮.
Yes, sir.
浠濡瑕涓蹇.
I need a fucking drink.
- 冲诲?- 诲借.
- Where do you wanna go? - Anywhere.
烩剧规按.
I'm gonna go get a table.
- 杩涓瀹涓轰.- 璋㈣阿
- I guess it's on me. - Thanks.
- 瑕逛涔? - 涓ゆら
- What'll it be? - Two beers.
濂界锛椹涓.
Yes, immediately.
缁.
give.
璋㈣阿
Thank you.
虫界.
I want a cigarette so bad.
姊?
Macer?
?
Yeah?
涓娆㈣磋涓锛浣瑙寰...
I hate to go on about this,
浣搴璇ヤㄦ蹇哥跺.
but I think the bra situation's the least of your problems.
濂藉...
Okay...
涓轰ュㄥ.
'Cause you look like shit.
. 浣璧锋ュㄥ. 缁姣涓浜洪借涔璇.
You do. You look like shit. Everybody on the team's talkin' about it.
濂规剧涔绉
They're like, "Kate used to be a number one draft pick.
濡浠璧锋ュ村涓ㄥ.
"Now look at her. She looks like fuckin' shit."
浣姣涔诲涓㈢.
Look at you. Your eyebrows are a mess.
涓锛瀹浠涓!
No, they're not!
瀹浠璧锋ュ氨姣姣锛灏斤璇烽浣浠浠涔?
They're like caterpillars, like wild beasts. You're losing weight...
涓...
I'm eating.
浣绠涓浠Tよ～绌夸涓?
Look at you. What is it, one T-shirt a week?
姣澶╅借锛?
At least work on your personal hygiene, huh?
浣璧锋ュ氨濡.
You sound like my mother.
涔璁告灏辨浣濡.
Maybe I am your mother.
浠.跺婚瓒甯.
First we work on personal hygiene, then we move on to the shopping.
缁浣涔颁璞锛? 澶涓
Get you some potatoes, yeah? Eat some food...
浣甯板浜?杩浠涔版?
Where have you taken me? What is this place?
涓涓.
It's a bar.
杩ㄦ浠
It's full o' cowboys.
涓涓浠
I'm a cowboy.
浣涓涓涔″反浣.
You're a redneck.
涔涓涓涔″反浣. 濞朵濠.
I'm a redneck. Got a trailer. Got a wife.
浣ㄨ蹭涔?
What are you talking about?
涓涓寰, 濞朵涓涓濠锛浠濡瑰.
I got a trailer, I got a wife. She's my sister.
峰!
Hey, Reg.
- 娉板痉锛 - 浜浠涔浜锛
- Ted! - What's goin' on?
- ! 濂戒涓瑙! - 瑙颁濂斤浼璁.
- Long time. How you been? - Yeah, it's good to see you, man.
浣杩寰涔?
Good to see you, too. How you been?
浣浠淇╁ㄥㄨ捣锛?
Gettin' your groove on, huh?
浠涓锛姝ｈ寮濮.
We're just startin'. We just got here.
浣涓甯浠缁涓涓?
All right. You gonna introduce me, man?
瑰痉锛杩孤锋. 妗.
Ted, Phoenix PD, Kate, my partner.
浣濂藉? 瑕娉板痉 灏辨病崇郴
How you doin'? Just Ted, it's fine.
杩浣╄蒋.
I saw you play softball once.
杞?
Softball?
濂硅寸ｆ父锛瑰痉.
She was at the game, Ted.
娓告?
"The game?"
涓哄, ㈤,
Where you struck out in slow-pitch softball.
浣╁轰.
You played really, really well.
у伴ｈ竟.
I appreciate that.
寰浼借蜂浠涓杞?
I'm gonna head back to that bar now. Can I get y'all another round?
浠ワ娌￠棰.
Yeah, sure.
濂界
All right.
浠浜轰.
Ted, he's a good guy.
句杩╂锛椹涓灏卞ソ.
Just give me one second, I'll be right with you.
ㄨ? 澶濂戒.
All right...
绛绛锛绛绛.
Just wait, wait a second...
涔浜? 浣硅浜.
What, what? Is it too much?
瑕涓规堕存虫.
Just wait one minute. I just need a second.
辨..辨...
All right. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
.
Hey, Kate?
匡杩ワ杩.
Hey! Hey, come here, stop, stop, talk to me.
浠锛濂藉? 炬剧.
Just talk to me. Okay? Relax. Okay? Just take it...
璇ユ. 癸
Whoa, shit! Kate...
杩涔浜?杩.
What is it? What? Stop.
涓...涓...
Stop. Stop.
浣浠濡ㄥ浠涔?
Shit, what the fuck! What did you...
- 涓瑕...- 浠濡浣瑕骞蹭涔
- Don't... - What the fuck are you...
璇ユ
God damn!
浣虫浜? 浣浠濡浜!?
You fuckin' try to shoot me? You fuckin' crazy?
- 涓! - 璁╂璧.
- Stop that! - Get off me!
浠濡...
Fuck that...
璇ユ荤  浣浠濡浣
Damn it, Kate! Just fucking stop!
浣
Stop!
涓.
Stop, bitch! Stop! Fuck!
浠濡涓!
Fuckin' stop!
浣
Stop.
濡
Fuck!
杩芥浣. 浣宠杩涔
This is you, you hear me? You did this. You did this.
浣挎褰璇遍サ
You used me as bait.
浣宸卞璇遍サ.
Nah, you used yourself as bait.
璇杩浣锛璧拌惰.
I told you not to go in the bank.
浣琚浠涓浜锛骞稿ソ..姝姝ｇ.
You brought him back here, though. That was smart.
, 璁╂浠瑁涓涓ㄥ烘.
Yeah. Love how we're gonna pretend like I planned this.
ｄュ灏辨杩涔.
Why don't you just write that in your report.
ュ. 杩涓濂芥.
Come on! This is good news!
寰蹇浠浠灏变煎灏路杩浜瑰.
They're gonna call Manuel back soon.
绐存ц灞灏辫ヤ.
Isn't that the point?
娌′锛峰.
It's okay, Reg.
剧瑙寰浠涓.
I thought he was a friend.
ラ.
I know.
- 浣虫浠涓ュ? - 涓.寰濂
- Want me to stay tonight? - No. I'm good.
- 纭瀹? - 纭瀹
- You sure? - I'm good.
浣虫璇浣, 浣浠濡涓村ㄦ.
How y'all want me to talk to you when you keep fuckin' hittin' me?
杩澶灏浣杩风ョ璀璐ョ被琚杈瑰瀵归㈤ｄ浜烘朵拱浜?
How many other corrupt motherfuckers are you workin' with on this side of the border?
濂藉......濂戒.
All right. Look...
, 灏卞璇寸ｆ.
It's exactly what I told you, all right?
浠浠句锛璁╂ㄨ杈瑰府瑰.
They came to me and they wanted details about our case,
绛搴浜, ｆ涓烘涓虫浜哄姝ゅ颁激瀹.
and yes, I did it, I gave it to them, but I never wanted anybody to get hurt.
涔涓浼昏杩瓒娴姘翠.
I would have never gotten involved with them pieces of shit
濡涓鸿や负浠讳...
if I thought that there was any...
......濂藉...濂藉!
Fuck! Okay! Fuck! Okay!
濂戒锛杩浜涓浠崇ラ锛瑰痉.
"Okay, okay, okay," is not what we're lookin' for, Ted.
灏界′琚浜涓琛娣澶达浣浠跺寰涓.
You know what the beauty is of you being so beat to a pulp?
浣ラ锛娌′汉浼浠浣澶浜灏.
'Cause no one's gonna notice a few more scratches.
杩绗颁氦, 瑰痉.
This is a new deal, Ted.
浠ュ冲浣濂冲挎藉峰淇.
I'm the one who decides whether your daughter'll get Federal protection,
浠濡
Fuck...
涔浠ュ冲浣濡荤板惧扮涓.
or whether we post your ex-wife's address on the Internet.
杩浠ュ冲锛浣琚杩涓涓瀵浜ラｆ风㈡,
I decide whether you go to prison in a work camp in Missouri,
杩涓涓灏灞.
or a kill house like Corcoran.
濂界
All right.
浣讳浠锛充浣锛.
This is where you negotiate how to survive, my friend.
濂藉.浣...
Okay. Look...
宠辫涓.
I feel like this whole thing's just gotten away from me...
存镐. 板ㄦ澶撮藉ぇ浜.
I fucked up. Okay, I fucked up and I'm in over my fuckin' head right now.
寰辨
I'm sorry...
璇ユ!璁╀浣! 璇ユ荤!
Fuck it! Get it out! Get it the fuck out!
璁╀浣! 璁╀浣! 璇ユ荤!
Fuck! Get it the fuck out! Get it out!
浣杩娣疯! 浣濡!
Motherfucker! And fuck you!
!
Fuck!
杩澶灏瀹琚榛甯朵拱浜?
How many officers do they have working on the force?
浠讳浣崇ラ藉璇浣
I'll tell you anything you wanna know.
瑕浣淇璇 濂冲跨瀹锛濂藉?
You just gotta promise me that my daughter's gonna be safe, okay?
浣瑕淇璇.
You make me that promise.
浣冲瀹璇?
You want the truth?
姹浣浜.
Please.
浣杩锋块甯界...
Give me all the names
...ョ瀹瀛锛璇村烘.
of all the motherfuckers they got working on the force.
濂界..濂界.
Okay, okay...
- 濂藉? - 濂界.
- All right? - Okay...
. 浠浠涓哄濮?
Okay. So, which phone do we start with?
灏辨ｄ釜. 渚垮
It's in that one. That shitty one.
- 杩涓渚垮 ? - .
- That's the shitty one? - Yes, sir!
板ㄦ瑙?
How you feelin'?
濂界逛.
Better.
. 浣搴璇ュ灏浠.
Well, you should've shot him.
涓杩冲..ヤ...
I just tried to have sex with my hitman.
浠骞朵虫浣.
Nah. He's no assassin.
浠宠锛浣ラ浜澶灏.
He just wanted to know what you know.
浠浠澶存浠锛涓浣.
They're after us, not you.
璋㈣阿.
Thank you.
浣璁╂宠捣涓瀵规瑷瑰浜.
You remind me of someone very special to me.
濂藉ソ′涓瑙.
Get some rest.
澶╁浠浠杩澧ㄨタョ跺锛
Tomorrow they'll call Manuel Diaz back to Mexico,
浠浼灏浠浠杩规璧.
and we'll cut a leg from them.
纭璁ょ. 惧ぇ惧.
We have eyes on the objective. Can we get a closer visual?
涓10绫.
Ten meters going by the eastern ridge.
哥?
Papa?
楦¤.
- 杈ｇ? - 褰.
浣浠澶╄涓?
涓.
浣瑕诲韪㈢?
- 韪㈢? - 锛哥.
- Football? - S铆, Papa.
棣寰℃胯.
濂藉э浠.
涓.
No!
姘歌戒纰板.
浜?
杩ュ.
Come on in.
缇崇楗锛
Tasty beverage?
濂藉锛浼璁′滑...
Okay, boys.
杩涔浜? 浣浠璁″瑕骞蹭涔?
What's going on? What's the plan?
浠瑕寮濮╃浜.
We're going hunting.
煎灏路杩浜硅ㄨ韩杩澧ㄨタヤ.
Looks like Manuel Diaz is being called back to Mexico.
浠姝ｅㄧ‘璁.
Just waiting for confirmation.
杩灏辨ч锛杩.
There's the tunnel right there.
濂藉э濂戒
All right, listen up.
璁╂浠娓澶寸华
Let's clarify the op.
浠瑕纭瀹浣缃 缁х画杩
We're gonna drive to location, proceed on foot...
- 浣濂藉? - 寰濂斤浣?
- How are you? - Good. How are you?
- 涔.- 浣瀛娌′?
- I'm fine. - How's the neck?
濂藉浜锛璋㈣阿.
It's better, thank you.
ｅ氨濂.
Good, good.
ч璺绾垮惧凡缁缁跺ソ
These diagrams are based on other tunnels that have been mapped.
骞堕绮剧‘板撅浠渚.
They're for reference only, they're not accurate.
褰浠佃揪杈瑰跺.浼涓涓涓存惰借
Once on the Mexican side of the border, there'll be a small staging area,
娌跨荤澶寸瑰寰浠浠姣浠搴.
then another shaft will lead to the main warehouse
浜濡ュ杩澧ㄨタ.
and the road that returns to Mexico.
ｉ浼寰澶姣楠″锛浠涓甯浠ュ℃浼.
Once we clear the mules, we don't expect more than a dozen bandits.
涓锛浠浠ㄥㄨタヨ圭杞ヨ姣.
No, they use Mexican police for vehicle transport.
濡浣浠ㄩч扮┛璀锛ｈ瀹璺浠浠涓浼.
If you see a uniform in the tunnel, consider him a bandit, too.
濂界...杩跺瑕璁ㄨ虹?
Okay. You want to discuss ROE?
娌′锛跺杩浜璇.
Nah, we'll save that for later.
濂界...
Okay.
ｅ氨澶ㄨ韩э㈠浠. 浠瑕澹颁昏タ
This is an in and out. We're clearing, placing an agent.
浠诲朵澶浠浠涓涓.
It's all about creating a diversion.
瑕堕涓涓澶у０斥.
Want the mother of all diversions, boys.
藉娆㈢澹伴抽ｄ澶.
Need a lot of noise. Fourth of July on steroids.
濂戒锛妫ュソ浣浠姝. ュэ浼璁′滑.
All right. Weapons check. Let's go, boys.
宸茬纭璁.
This looks like confirmation.
- 浠寰绱ц杈杞. - 娌￠锛蹇椤荤.
- I need to fit your guy with a locator. - Yeah, do it.
杩归㈡浠涓瀹讹浠浼瀹.
Those are Special Ops. Are we going in on this?
浣浠杩娌℃瑁澶.
Nah. You guys aren't really dressed for it.
涓轰涔浣涓璇浠
You didn't fuckin' tell us.
ㄥぉ浣浠淇╀釜寰姝讳逛技锛
Yeah, well, you two went cryin' to Daddy yesterday, and we
- 浠ユ病璇浣浠.- 缁涓涓绐村
- don't want Daddy to know everything. - Give me a fucking break!
荤浣浠夸瑁澶.
All right, we'll get you some extra gear.
浠瑁澶惧ㄨ溅.
We have tac gear in the car.
澶妫浜锛ｆ浠灏辨绱ф堕撮冲.
All right. Good. You guys will hang back when we get there, okay?
涓轰涔浠?
Then why are we going?
涓哄娌℃朵垮烘浜洪琛锛CIA涓藉ㄧ藉藉娉琛.
'Cause CIA can't operate within US borders
浠浠ㄥ藉娌℃杩ョ
without a domestic agency attached.
璇磋浣浠ㄧ.
I told you you'd be useful.
浠ヨ灏辨浠ㄨ.
So, that's it. That's why I'm here.
锛瀹ㄦｇ‘.
Yeah, that's it.
杩灏辨浣浠ㄨ.
That's why you're here.
濡版锛璁板ㄩㄦ病.
Hey, we find any drugs, you guys get to confiscate 'em.
杩灏浼缇濡涓澶.
It's gonna be a big day.
绠翠㈢镐俊.
Un-fuckin' real!
姝ｉ㈠
Front and back.
癸绠浜. 璁╀浠宸卞绘. 浠浠ㄥ╃ㄦ浠.
Kate, come on. Fuck these people, man. They've been using us from the beginning.
浠娌″瑕璺.
We don't have to do this.
蹇椤绘娓妤翠欢浜.
I need to know what they used us for.
- ｅ凡缁璋浜. - 璋锛
- Doesn't matter what! - Yes, it does!
杩. 浠绂诲杩锛璁╀浠ㄩ借楝煎诲.
I say we walk and make them eat this whole fucked-up operation.
涓锛蹇椤绘娓妤.
No. I have to know.
杞杈锛榛插椹帮杞RIN31B7.
Black Mercedes... Plate number: Romeo-India-November-
姝ｅㄥ涓瑰琛椹.
three-one-Bravo-seven. Heading south by southeast.
ㄥ?
Where?
ラ浜.
Okay.
浠寰蹇硅刀伴ч.
We gotta hit the tunnel the minute we get on the ground.
杩涓寰浜锛?
Pretty exciting, huh?
扮瑰ㄥ?
What is the target's location?
璇哄辨14. 寰瑗胯蛋.
14 miles south of Nogales heading west rapidly.
寮淇╂. ｆ涓.
Keep your fuckin' safeties on, barrels pointed down.
寰ㄥ锛
Stay in the back.
涔卞.  娓妤浜?
Don't shoot anyone on my fuckin' team. Right?
妫ヨ澶.
Gear check?
妫ョ浠.
Thermal camera check.
妫ュ瑙.
Night vision goggles check.
淇寮舵.
Get those guys.
浣甯A锛甯B.
Wanna take Alpha squad, I'll take B squad?
- 灏辨т璇寸 寮濮 - 琛ㄥ 瀛╁浠
- You got it. Let's do it. - Let's go, boys.
50绫 涓归瑰
Fifty meters. Your three o'clock, Alpha.
宸叉ヨ.
Stand by. Getting close to objective.
A锛B锛娉ㄦ. 12绫.
Alpha, Bravo, be advised. 12 meters straight ahead.
缁х画杩锛婧杩伙磋虫惧颁搴涓蹇.
All right, we need to boogie and we need to do it quiet till we find the center.
娉ㄦ哄０.
Draw the fighters to you and make some noise.
璺锛藉浠.
Don't follow me. I'll be fine.
诲昏?
What are the rules of engagement?
灏芥寮锛浼璁.
Weapons free, my friend. Weapons free.
灏芥寮锛灏瀹朵浠.
Weapons free, boys.
绁濂借
Good luck.
澶╁
Oh, God!
- 浣杩濂藉? - 娌′.
- You okay? - My gun!
璺ㄦ.
Leave it. Stay on my six.
蹇癸蹇癸
蹇ュ府蹇.
- ュ缁. - 涓琛.
- ュ缁! - 烽锛
涓捐捣!
杞杩韬!
楹寰锋?
!
Freeze!
惧浠.
Step away from him.
句. 惧浠.
Put that down.
璁ょ 绂讳杩
I mean it! Move away from him right now!
涓瑕挎瀵圭.
Don't ever point a weapon at me again.
ｆ锛跺ч.
Catch your breath. Then get back up there.
浣惧ㄦ瑰涓!
杩讳. 浣ラ逛?
I am through. Do you have my location?
ラ. ㄧ浣. ㄤ涓瑰.
Roger, we have you. Target is east and north of you.
17峰介. 浠ヤ56峰介寰涓绘浠.
Looks like Highway 56 to 17. Will intercept him if he stays on 17.
2 56峰介
Go east on 56 off Highway 2.
跺.
Wilco.
- 浣浠涔瀛? - 瑗垮缁村ゥ.
瑗垮缁村ゥ锛杞寮涓56峰介.
涓垮.
板ㄤ涓芥涓轰浣瀹朵汉.
浠ｈ竟峰?
Is he through yet?
浠宸茬GPS浼杩讳.
We have joy. GPS is transmitting. Audio is transmitting.
ヤ衡℃锛浠.
That was a clean, clean fucking op, my friend.
ゆ浜涓や釜娣疯
Except for these two assholes.
ｄ 浣濂介版捣澶 朵涓ㄤ绠
Well, you're better overseas. You don't have to babysit.
瑰ㄥ?
Where's Kate?
浣甯璺.
I thought she was with you.
浠寰绘惧ス
We gotta go back.
浠濡锛灏瀹朵浠锛浠涓浜涓涓浜猴璧板.
Shit. Boys, we're missin' one. Let's go.
Hey!
涓锛甯! 澶浜!
Just lay back, baby. Let it happen.
澶浜! 涓!
Stop! Stop!
惧
Get off me!
涓! 涓! 璇峰杩!
Stop moving! Stop!
涓!
Stop it.
烽! 烽!
Just relax. Just relax.
濂戒? 涓.
All right? You gonna stay there?
藉瑰?
Are you gonna stay there?
濂戒.
All right.
炬剧逛.
Now, you listen.
浣璧伴浜ч.
You went up the wrong tunnel.
浣颁浣涓璇ョ扮涓瑗.
You saw things you shouldn't have seen.
楹寰锋浠涔?
What is Medell铆n?
楹寰锋?
Medell铆n?
楹寰锋涓涓跺伙锛楹寰锋锛ヤ鸡姣浜璐╂锛
Medell铆n refers to a time
褰变浠ュ姣璐告跺锛
when one group controlled every aspect of the drug trade,
存╀寤虹璧蜂濂渚夸浠х绉╁.
providing a measure of order that we could control.
灏甯娲句村缃锛璁╂涓瀹瀹搴.
And until somebody finds a way to convince 20% of the population
村版涓ヤ浜哄搁ｄ灞涓瑗.
to stop snorting and smoking that shit,
绉╁浠界姹濂芥娈.
order's the best we can hope for.
浣搴璇ョ颁
And what you saw up there,
浜妗寰风姝ｆ浠浠娲炬ユ寤鸿涓绉╁.
was Alejandro working toward returning that order.
浜妗寰风浠濡ㄥ府ヤ鸡姣浜璐╂㈠浜.
Alejandro works for the fucking Colombian Cartel.
甯浠浜哄浜.
He works for the competition.
浜妗寰风浠ュ府浠讳浜哄浜.
Alejandro works for anyone
瑕浜烘句 浠灏变涓鸿浜
who will point him toward the people who made him.
浠...
Us.
浠浠...
Them.
瑕藉府浠浣ｄ釜...
Anyone who will turn him loose.
浠濡诲澶寸涓ャ
So, he can get the person that cut off his wife's head,
骞朵浠濂冲挎杩涓妗剁～搁㈢浜.
and threw his daughter into a vat of acid.
...
Yeah.
浠涓杩浜稿╃.
That's what we're dealing with.
浣涓介ｄ.
You can't do this.
浣涓.
You can't.
寰纭瀹浣浠杩ㄥ榛藉剧浜虹惧.
I'm sure as shit not the person you're gonna hide it all behind.
板锛璇捐交剧
You need to just take a breath.
浠濡瑕璇村烘.
I'm gonna fuckin' talk.
- 涓锛浣涓浼. - 浼.
- No, you're not. - Yeah.
瑕浣浠浣涓哄璇镐浼.
I'm gonna tell everyone what you did.
浣杩涔灏卞お涓轰
That would be a major mistake.
ㄦ瑰? 娌￠
Is that the target up ahead? Confirm.
榛插椹板氨ㄤ60绫.
Roger that. Black Mercedes, 60 meters ahead.
瑗垮缁村ゥ锛
Silvio...
蹇.
板锛寮璀锛
浣灏卞揩涓ｈ杞浜.
浣杩涓娣疯!
This motherfucker...
澶濂戒.
- 寮澹板锛浠涓杞.
涓杞.
.
浠浣杞婊烘!
浠寮澶濂锛跺杞韬.
寮澶濂锛跺杞韬.
浣ラ璋?
璁╀ラ锛浠濂戒涔у.
浣涓ョ.
寮澶濂锛跺杞韬.
- 浠. - !
浣涓涓濂借瀵锛瑗垮缁村ゥ.
板ㄥ颁涓杞.
涓杞锛瑗垮缁村ゥ.
浣瑕骞蹭涔?
杩ワョ! 浣ラ璋?
- 涓涓榛甯澶! - 瓒村ㄥ颁! 瓒村ㄥ颁!
, ラ浣璋.
浣涓璋璇杩绡
涓瀛姘寸浜.
板锛浣璇ュ诲浣胯涓浜.
璧锋!
濡浣㈣交涓惧锛浣濂冲垮氨浼琚20涓蜂汉杞濂歌存.
杞杩韬.
涓杞.
- 煎灏路杩浜. - 璁よ浣.
煎灏...稿硅浜.
浣冲讳瀹跺浠涔?
What happens when we get to the house?
ㄩㄥｆ杞涓锛寰涓杞浜.
You'll stop the car, I'll get out.
瑰颁涔浜浜?
What will happen to me?
浣涓澶.
Slow it down.
杩浜瑰?
杩6涓.
Six remain.
浠抽璁浜.
We're going blind.
ｄ.
缁х画锛涓朵浼浜浠.
杩浜瀛╁寰辫?
涓.
No.
ｆ浠ㄨ辫璇.
缁х画锛缁х画.
姣涓锛澶灏瀹跺涵浣瀹剁翠汉浜.
Every night you have families killed.
浣锛村ㄨ瀹浜椁.
And yet, here you dine.
浠浼浜涓.
Tonight should be no different.
缁х画.
ｄ娲句ヨ浜
Do you think the people that sent you here
浠浠浠涔涓?
are any different?
浣ラ浠浣韬涓颁浠涔?
Who do you think we learned it from?
涓涓璐濠寰甯.
The grieving lawyer...
浣濡诲...濂逛涓轰板ㄨ涓峰伴插?
Your wife, you think she'd be proud of what you've become?
蹇浜濂冲.
Don't forget about my daughter.
锛浣濂冲.
浣涔村苟涓绉浜烘╂.
瀵规ヨ达.
浼ゅ虫垮.
Not in front of my boys.
跺绘ュ涓甯ユ扁浜.
缁х画锛ㄥ浣椁.
Go ahead and finish your meal.
浠濂藉绔ㄩ冲颁锛.
I would recommend not standing on balconies for a while, Kate.
涓.
Sit down.
浣璧锋ュ涓灏濂冲.
You look like a little girl when you're scared.
浣璁╂宠捣ｅけ讳濂冲.
You remind me of the daughter they took away from me.
瑕浣ㄨ寮绾镐㈢惧.
I need you to sign this piece of paper.
纭璁ゆ浠琛ㄦ娉.
It basically says that everything we did
蹇椤昏涔㈡浠
was done by the book.
涓界.
I can't sign that.
绛句瀹.
Sign it.
娌′.
It's okay.
涓界捐瀛.
I can't sign that.
澶╁.
God!
㈢琛涓猴.
You would be committing suicide, Kate.
ュэ绛句瀹.
Come on. Sign it.
宠锋浣宸辫讳涓灏
You should move to a small town,
浠娉寰姝ｄ瀛ㄧ灏.
where the rule of law still exists.
ㄨ浣娉瀛涓.
You will not survive here.
浣骞朵.
You are not a wolf.
杩肩兢棰帮
And this is the land of wolves now.
璋㈣阿瑙璧
靛奖 BT棣璁哄
www.BTshoufa.com